rallysportdirect.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy

### **INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**

[RallySportDirect.com](http://www.rallysportdirect.com/) is the sole owner of consumer information collected through this website. We do not and will not sell or rent this information to any outside parties under any circumstances. We collect information from you, our customers, solely to process orders and provide you with pertinent information such as order confirmations and order status updates. Information collected on our Site includes but is not limited to your name, email address, billing and shipping addresses, telephone number(s), and payment information such as your credit card number.

**ACCOUNT REGISTRATION**

To better process orders placed through this website, we ask that you complete a short registration form during checkout. During the registration process, you will be required to submit your name, email address, street address, and telephone number. We use this contact information to provide important [RallySportDirect.com](http://www.rallysportdirect.com/) services, including automated order updates sent via email. We may also use this information to contact you if we have any problems processing your order. Before the registration process is complete, you will be asked to submit a password of your choice for future access to your account settings and history. To ensure your account information remains confidential, do not share your username or password with anyone. If you forget your password and would like to have it emailed to you, you may use the "Forgot Password" feature located on our login page. If you forget both your username and your password, please contact our Customer Service Department for assistance. 

#### **ORDER PAYMENT**

In addition to the information provided during the registration process, you will be asked to provide certain financial information, such as your credit card number and expiration date, before we can finalize your order. This information is collected for payment purposes only. To gain proper authorization and transaction approval, we must submit your personal and financial information to our merchant bank. This process is carefully protected by an enhanced security system to ensure the safety of your information. We do not share your personal or financial information with any third parties, except those specified in the Information Sharing section below. 

**WEBSITE COOKIES**

A cookie is a small text file placed on your hard drive to store information. [RallySportDirect.com](http://www.rallysportdirect.com/) customizes certain page content based on your browser type and other information provided by our cookies. We will not share any personally identifiable information provided by a cookie with any third party; we will, however, link data stored in the cookie to the personally identifiable information you submitted through our Site. This allows us to personalize your shopping experience and discern user preferences. The [RallySportDirect.com](http://www.rallysportdirect.com/) Shopping Cart feature also uses cookie technology to save account registration information and to retain your order history for future account access. If you choose to disable cookie functionality, you may still browse our store; however, you will be unable to use the Shopping Cart, and thus [RallySportDirect.com](http://www.rallysportdirect.com/) will be unable to accept your online order. 

**LOG FILES**

We use computer IP addresses to administer the Site, track user movement, analyze trends, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We do not link any IP addresses to personally identifiable information, and we do not distribute or share IP information with any third parties. 

**EXTERNAL LINKS**

[RallySportDirect.com](http://www.rallysportdirect.com/) contains links to other sites that are not monitored by or protected under our Privacy Policy. [RallySportDirect.com](http://www.rallysportdirect.com/) is not responsible for the privacy practices of external sites, and we encourage users leaving our Site to read the privacy statements of every website that collects personally identifiable information. 

#### **INFORMATION SHARING**

We may employ third party companies to perform certain designated functions on our behalf. These functions relate to order fulfillment, package and postal delivery, email delivery, customer service, data analysis, and credit processing. The third parties we contract for these purposes have limited access to your personal information and may not use it for any reason other than those we have previously delimited. In the event of a product recall, we may disclose your contact information to the product manufacturer(s) in the interest of consumer safety. We also reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law, and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website. 

**PROMOTIONAL MATERIAL**

To honor the privacy of our users, promotional communications from [RallySportDirect.com](http://www.rallysportdirect.com/) are only sent to those customers who wish us to do so. If you would like to change the email address where such information is sent, you may update your preferences by following the website link embedded in any promotional email. You may also choose to add a secondary email address by signing up for our mailing list using that address. If you no longer wish to receive any electronic news updates or special offer notices from [RallySportDirect.com](http://www.rallysportdirect.com/), you may opt-out using the link at the bottom of any promotional email. Customers who have chosen to opt-out of receiving promotional material will still receive order confirmations and order status updates via email. 

**CUSTOMER REVIEWS**

The Customer Review section of [RallySportDirect.com](http://www.rallysportdirect.com/) was created for the purpose of sharing positive experiences and providing useful product feedback. The posted reviews are not edited or altered by [RallySportDirect.com](http://www.rallysportdirect.com/) in any way, but their content is moderated to ensure accuracy and appropriateness. [RallySportDirect.com](http://www.rallysportdirect.com/) reserves the right to post or remove any review at its discretion. By posting your comment(s) and/or review(s) (collectively, "Customer Review") on our Site, you give us permission to reprint or use the Customer Review in connection with our business and agree to the following conditions: (1) The Customer Review will be reprinted and/or used solely at our discretion and does not involve compensation; (2) We may use the Customer Review with or without any pseudo (pen) name credit; (3) Our right to use the Customer Review is perpetual and may be assigned by us; (4) We may use the Customer Review locally, nationally, or globally and such use may be made in any media, information, or communication platform (including Internet advertising) currently in use or later developed; and (5) You (not someone else) composed and posted the Customer Review. Other than your pseudo (pen) name, which we may or may not use, your personal contact information will not be disclosed in connection with our reprint or use of your Customer Review. 

**USE BY MINORS**

[RallySportDirect.com](http://www.rallysportdirect.com/) is committed to protecting the welfare and privacy of children and minors. We will not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information via the Internet from children under the age of 13. We do not sell products for purchase by children, and youth-oriented products are sold for purchase by adults only. Youth under the age of 18 may only use [RallySportDirect.com](http://www.rallysportdirect.com/) in the presence of a consenting parent or guardian. 

* * *

**CONDITION OF USE**

By visiting or purchasing from [RallySportDirect.com](http://www.rallysportdirect.com/), you agree to abide by our terms and conditions, including those set forth in this privacy statement. Any revisions to our Privacy Policy will be posted on this page and any other page we deem necessary to inform our users of any changes in the type of information we collect, how we use that information, and under what circumstances, if any, we may disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of the Site following any policy revisions constitutes your acceptance of and agreement with the changes made. If you have any questions about our privacy practices that have not been addressed in this Privacy Policy, please contact our Customer Service Department for assistance. 

OUR ADDRESS

RallySportDirect.com   
4870 W. 2100 S.   
Suite A   
Salt Lake City, UT 84120   

LAST UPDATE 

Privacy Policy - Last Revised: May 21, 2015.
